<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about_us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ Solutions Ltd&lt;/tooltip&gt; is a premier supplier of turnkey data acquisition products and services. &lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; specialises in high quality simultaneous digitisers, featuring high channel count, deep capture memory and open standard interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Formed in 1999, we were initially active in supplying networked transient recorders based on ACQ32PCI to diagnostic applications in Plasma Fusion research. Since then we have supplied many hundreds of channels for high speed diagnostic experiments to research installations around the world, where our products&amp;rsquo; high channel density, simultaneous capture capability, Open Source software platform and value for money is appreciated. Plasma Fusion diagnostics are still a major market for &lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt;, to which we&amp;rsquo;ve added support for innovative applications in Plasma Control and many other other market areas in research and test and measurement. The latest generation of products, capable of standalone networked operation, with further gains in channel density and reductions in cost per channel are opening up new market areas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/intelligent_digitizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/intelligent_digitizers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;intelligent-digitizer-concept&#34;&gt;Intelligent Digitizer Concept&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; digitizers feature an array of discrete &lt;tooltip title=&#34;Analog to Digital Convertor&#34;&gt;ADC&lt;/tooltip&gt; devices, one convertor per channel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This differs from most digitizer cards, which will use a single &lt;tooltip title=&#34;Analog to Digital Convertor&#34;&gt;ADC&lt;/tooltip&gt; device with a multiplexer to route each channel in sequence onto the &lt;tooltip title=&#34;Analog to Digital Convertor&#34;&gt;ADC&lt;/tooltip&gt; in turn. The &lt;tooltip title=&#34;Analog to Digital Convertor&#34;&gt;ADC&lt;/tooltip&gt;-per-channel approach became cost-effective with the advent of fast and accurate integrated &lt;tooltip title=&#34;Successive Approximation Register (class of ADC with Excellent DC accuracy)&#34;&gt;SAR&lt;/tooltip&gt; convertor devices, and offers the following advantages over the multiplexer approach:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;we-support-open-standards-and-open-source-software&#34;&gt;We support Open Standards and Open Source Software.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is &lt;tooltip&gt;DTACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; policy to supply full documentation to all interfaces and the source code to working examples  to customers on request. In addition, the majority of the operating software is made available to customers as source code under the &lt;tooltip&gt;GPL&lt;/tooltip&gt;. Where products are deployed with a host side driver, this driver is supplied for the user&amp;rsquo;s Linux host system as source code, licensed under the &lt;tooltip&gt;GPL&lt;/tooltip&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/architecture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;architecture&#34;&gt;Architecture&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; 4G digitizers use the Xilinx ZYNQ system on chip providing high performance at low cost.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; 2G digitizers conform to recognized industrial standards, and are designed to work in standard chassis. In common with most other digitizer cards, they can work as peripheral devices under the control of a system master computer in the chassis. New &lt;tooltip title=&#34;D-TACQ High Performance Simultaneous Data Acquisition&#34;&gt;D-TACQ&lt;/tooltip&gt; 4G products are available both as discrete analog modules, available to plug into third party standards-compliant sites, and as 1U rack-mount appliances.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
